<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jake Waddle&#39;s Data Blog</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jake Waddle&#39;s Data Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>Shoot me a note If you&amp;rsquo;d like to collaborate on a sports project or have a question, feel free to send me a note on LinkedIn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Me</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>What is this? I&amp;rsquo;ve put off organizing rmarkdown documents into a blog for far too long. Initially, the objective for this repository of blurbs is to publish tutorials, exploratory analyses, and statistical modeling exercises. More often than not, the data used will be sports or stock market related. I created this blog using the blogdown package.
A little about me, I guess Hi, my name is Jake Waddle. I live in Fort Smith, Arkansas with my wife and two little golden nuggets of joy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gathering Historical NFL Weather Data</title>
      <link>/post/gathering-historical-nfl-weather-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/gathering-historical-nfl-weather-data/</guid>
      <description>Warmish WelcomeFantasy sports are a passion of mine because they reside at the intersection of two of my favorite things in the world: sports and data. Over the last 4 or so years, I have built data sets suitable for modeling fantasy football and basketball outcomes. I tend to favor daily fantasy, but weather data is valuable for season long fantasy football as well.
In fantasy football, weather data are valuable for a variety of reasons.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
